Willowbrook Review Panel; Records apap127
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED], 1968-1981; 7; 12.9 cubic ft.
  - Willowbrook Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1968-1981; 7.1; 8.3 cubic ft.
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Staff Training Program Manual for Development Plan Implementation [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Staffing, Absenteeism [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Willowbrook Developmental center, Staffing, Direct Care Staffing Summary Weekly Averages [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Staffing In-Service/Training [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Staffing, Shortage [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Staffing Reports [RESTRICTED], 1978 July (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Administrative Polices and Procedures [RESTRICTED], 1975; 1977 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Case Conference [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Community Placement Plans [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Complaints [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Disaster Plan [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 2 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Policy and Procedure Manual, Unit 6 [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 3 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Residents Population List [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 3 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Training [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 3 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Various Items for the WRP [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 3 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center and State Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities, Ad Hoc Committee [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 3 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, "Wheelchair Crisis" [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 3 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Willowbrook Developmental center, United Cerebral Palsy, Incident Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 4 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Willowbrook Developmental center, United Cerebral Palsy, Incident Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 4 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Willowbrook Developmental center, United Cerebral Palsy, Incident Review Committee, Minutes [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 4 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy- In-service Documentation [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 4 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Job Descriptions, Manual of [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 4 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 4 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Unit Cerebral Palsy, Nursing Policy Manual [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 4 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Nursing Procedure Manual [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 4 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Behavior Modification [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Behavior Modification [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Building 2 [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Building 2 [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977; 1979; Undated (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Case Management Reports [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Class Member List Summary [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Class Member List Summary [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Class Member List Summary [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Client Death [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Client Goal Planning, Contract with Houts and Scott [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Clinical Control, Monitoring Activities [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Clinical Control, Monitoring Forms [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Clinical Control Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Clothing Situation [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Community Placement Service [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Community Store [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Consent Judgment Coordinator [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Continence Training Program [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Contracts, Outside [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Contracts and Proposals; Campbell, Magda [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Contracts and Proposals; Cohen, Ira Larry [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Contracts and Proposals, Management Analysis Center [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Contracts and Proposals, New York University Dental Center [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Contracts and Proposals, projected Expenditures [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Contracts and proposals, United States public health Service Hospital [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Correspondence, General [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Dental Services [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Deputy Director of Administrative Services [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Deputy Director of Clinical Services, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Director, Connon, Levester, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Director; Howe, Elin [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Director; Howe, Elin, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 5 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Director; Howe, Elin, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Director; Howe, Elin, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Doctor's Meeting of February 28 [RESTRICTED], 1977; 1975-1977 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Education [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Education [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Education [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978; Undated (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Education, Consultant's Report [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Education, Model Demonstration Program [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Emergency Strike Plan [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Employees Grade 7 and 9 Pool [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Environment [RESTRICTED], 1975; 1979 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Final Folders [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, ICFIMR Survey [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Incident Reports [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Incident Reports, Special Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Incident Reports, Special Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Incident Reports, Special Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Individual Placements [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Labor [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977; 1979 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Labor [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977; 1979 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Labor, Employee Relations, CSEA and UCP [RESTRICTED], 1977; 1979 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Legal Advisor Program [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Willowbrook developmental Center, Legal Advisor Program [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 6 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Maintenance Safety and Emergency Procedure [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Management [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Management [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Management Analysis Center [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Map of Grounds [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Medical Exemptions [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Medical and nursing Services [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Medical and Nursing Services [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Medical and Nursing Services [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Medical and Nursing Services [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Medical and Nursing Services, By-Laws [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Medical and Nursing Services, Dr. Feinberg [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Medical Plan [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Medical Plan, Exhibits [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Memoranda [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Mid-Level Health Staffing Compliance Information [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Missing Persons [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Missing Persons, Search Procedures [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Non-Residential Clients Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Non-Residential Clients Survey [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Operational Goals [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Opinion Questionnaire [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Personnel, Employee Complaints [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Personnel, In-service Training [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976; 1978-1979 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Physical Plant [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Piepenbrink and Slawski Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976; 1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Policies and Procedures [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Policies and Procedures Manual [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Policies and Procedures Manual Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Programming and Evaluation [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976; 1978-1979 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Progress Reports [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Projects, Status [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Psychiatric Services [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Psychiatric Services [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Quality of Life Monitoring System [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Recreation [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 7 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Resident Transfer [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Restraints and Abuses [RESTRICTED], 1976; 1978-1979 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Review of the Recruitment Problems Relating to Nurses, Occupational, and Physical Therapists [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Social Work Services [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Roosevelt/SIDC Medical Services [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Speech Pathology and Audiology Services [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Spending Plans [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970; 1972-1973 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Spending Plans [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Staffing [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Staffing, Mid-Level Supervisory Staff [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Staffing, Mid-Level Supervisory Staff [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Staffing, Staff Housing [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Toilet Training [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Toilet Training Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Toilet Training Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, Trans-Disciplinary Approach [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Budget Appeal/Shared Staff [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Client Deaths, Follow-Up Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Complaints and Inquiries: Karl Warner Center [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Information [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy, Min-Team Contract [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Willowbrook Developmental Center, United Cerebral Palsy at Nina Eaton Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (7-State Developmental Centers [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)